A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, The Fund for the Advancement of Education (TFAE) files FA740
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Awardees – Multi-Institutional (not Fund Administered), 1944-1966; III; 115.2 Cubic Feet 96 boxes.
  - Faculty Fellowship Program, 1950-1963; 7; 31.2 Cubic Feet 26 boxes.; 26 boxes.
    - FFP, 1954-1955, 1951-1957; Legal size.
      - Rhys, Hedley Howell - Swarthmore College, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Rix, Herbert David - Pennsylvania State University, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Robinson, William H. - Hampton Institute, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Roche, John Pearson - Haverford College, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Rossbach, George B. - West Virginia Wesleyan College, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Rozwenc, Edwin Charles - Amherst College, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Rubsamen, Walter Howard - California, University of, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Sabtino, Richard A. - Rhode Island, University of, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Sadler, Jefferson Davis - Furman University, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Sarason, Bertram D. - New Haven State Teachers College, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Saville, Lloyd Blackstone - Duke University, 1954-1956 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Schlegel, Marvin Wilson - Longwood College, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Schrader, Helen Wheatley - Stanford University, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Smiley, Malcolm Finlay - Iowa, State University of, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Smith, Barnett F. - Spelman College, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Smith, George Horsley - Rutgers University, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Smith, Victor E. - Michigan State College, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Spivack, Bernard - Fisk University, 1954-1956 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Stanford, Lyle Morris - Idaho, College of, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Starkman, Miriam Kosh - Queens College, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Steinhoff, William Richard - Michigan, University of, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Stocking, David Mackenzie - Beloit College, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Stowell, Ernest E. - Wisconsin State College, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Stroud, Theodore A. - Drake University, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Sutherland, Donald - Colorado, University of, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Sylvester, William Arthur - Kansas State College, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Talacko, Joseph Venceslas - Marquete University, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Talimadge, William Henry - New York, State University of, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Taylor, Dick - Tulane University, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Thomas, Earl - Vanderbilt University, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Thomas, Thurlo B. - Carleton Colege, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Townsend, James Benjamin - North Carolina, University of, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Trautman, Herman L. - Vanderbilt University, 1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Tredgold, Donald Warren - Washington, University of, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Treganza, Adan Eduardo - San Francisco State College, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Trimble, Harold C. - Iowa State Teachers College, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Turner, Merle B. - San Diego State College, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Vanderford, Joan C. - Del Mar College, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Van Ghent, Dorothy - Vermont, University of, 1951-1954 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Waterman, John T. - Southern California, University of, 1954-1955 (Box 20 (49681))
      - Watrous, James S. - Wisconsin, University of, 1954-1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Wheeler, Bernice Marian - Connecticut College, 1954-1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Wienpahl, Paul Develin - California, University of, 1954 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Williams, Eliot C. Jr. - Wabash College, 1954-1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Winship, George Parker Jr. - King College, 1954-1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Workman, John D. - Wisconsin, University of, 1954-1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Wrage, Ernest J. - Northwestern University, 1954 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Wray, William Rose - Oklahoma Baptist University, 1954 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Wyllie, Irvin Gordon - Missouri, University of, 1954 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Yalden-Thomson, David Cron - Virginia, University of, 1954 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Yohannan, John David - City College, 1954-1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Young, James Harvey - Emory University, 1954 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Zink, Sidney - Missouri, University of, 1954-1955 (Box 21 (49682))
    - FFP, 1955-1956, 1952-1963; Legal size.
      - Baird, James R. - Connecticut College, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Barnett, Milton L. - Wisconsin, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Baskerville, Barnet - Washington, University of, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Benson, Carl - Alabama Polytechnic Institute, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Berkowitz, Sol - Queens College, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Bierck, Harold Alfred Jr. - North Carolina, University of, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Bigger, Charles P. - Mississippi, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Blackman, Edward Bernard - Michigan State College, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Bowling, Lawrence Edward - Texas Technological College, 1962-1963 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Bredenberg, Paul A. - North Carolina State University, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Bruton, Henry Jackson - Yale University, 1954-1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Bryant, Billey Finney - Vanderbilt University, 1954-1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Burford, M. Gilbert - Wesleyan University, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Cardenas, Daniel N. - Oklahoma, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Carroll, Harry J. Jr. - Pomona College, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Carter, John Stewart - Chicago Teachers College, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Carter, Paul Jefferson Jr. - Colorado, Universtity of, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Chen, Henry S. C. - Drexel Institute of Technology, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Champigny, Robert J. - Indiana University, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Chou, I-Kua - William and Mary, College of, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Christopher, John B. - Rochester, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Cohen, Robert Sonne - Wesleyan University, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Cohen, Sanford - Western Reserve University, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Cordle, Thomas Howard - Duke University, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Dean, Howard Edward - Oregon, University of, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Dean, Leonard F. - Connecticut, University of, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Delanney, Louis Edgerton - Wabash College, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Denbow, Carl H. - Ohio University, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Dickson, David W. D. - Michigan State College, 1955 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Dragnich, Alex N. - Vanderbilt University, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Driscoll, Glen R. - South Dakota, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 21 (49682))
      - Eckardt, Arthur Roy - Lehigh University, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Elder, Robert Ellsworth - Colgate University, 1954-1957 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Finholt, Albert Edward - Saint Olaf College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Foose, Richard Martin - Franklin and Marshall College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Frank, Robert Worth - Illinois Institute of Technology, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Fuller, Homer Woodrow - University of Tennessee, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Gange, John Frederic - Universtity of Virginia, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Gerber, Helmut Emil - Lafayette College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Gibson, William Walker - Amherst College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Gillis, Everett Alden - Texas Techical College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Goedicke, Victor - Ohio University, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Grantham, Dewey W. Jr. - Vanderbilt University, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Gruber, Howard E. - University of Colorado, 1955-1957 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Haggh, Raymond H. - Memphis State College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Harrington, Fred Harvey - Wisconsin, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Harrison, John A. - University of Florida, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Hemmle, Gene L. - Texas Technical College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Henderson, David - Pittsburgh, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Hibben, Frank Cummings - New Mexico, University of, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Higginson, Fred H. - Kansas State College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Higham, John - Rutgers University, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Hinman, Robert B. - Rochester, University of, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Hobbs, Grimsley T. - Earlham College, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Holt, Perry C. - East Tennessee State College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Houghton, Walter Edwards - Wellesley College, 1954-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Humphreys, Mabel Gweneth - Randolph Macon Woman's College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Irwin, Vera R. - New York, State University of, 1955-1957 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Jansen, William Hugh - Kentucky, University of, 1955-1957 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Johanson, Ralph N. - Boston University, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Johnson, Leland Parrish - Drake University, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Jones, William Thomas - Pomona College, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Karush, William - Chicago, University of, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Keast, William R. - cornell University, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Kelly, Paul Joseph - University of California, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Lanyi, George Albert - Oberlin College, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Laycock, Frank - California, University of, 1952-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Lewis, Archibald Ross - Texas, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Lewis, Hylan G. - Atlanta University, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Lindberg, Arne O. - Washington College, State College of, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Liu, James T. - Pittsburgh, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Locher, Kaspar Theodore - Reed College, 1955 (Box 22 (49683))
      - Loftis, John C. Jr - Stanford University, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Long, Eugene Robert Jr. - North Carolina, University of, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Lytle, Scott - Washington, University of, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Marshall, James Fred - Whittier College, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Martin, Richard Milton - Pennsylvania, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Mason, Wilton Jr. - North Carolina, Unviersity of, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Melden, Abraham I. - Washington, University of, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Mercier, Vivian Herbert Samuel - City College, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Meyer, Frederick Robert - Rochester Institute of Technology, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Moore, Asher - Northwestern University, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Mussen, Paul Henry - Ohio State University, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Nielsen, Marion L. - Utah State Agricultural College, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Niven, Ivan Morton - University of Oregon, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Nolte, Eugene A. Jr. - Arkansas State Teachers College, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Oost, Stewart I. - Southern Methodist University, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Owen, David H. - Syracuse University, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Parnell, John V. Jr. - Virginia State College, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Pasquariello, Anthony M. - Michigan, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Patrick, John Max - Queens College, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Paul, Rodman W. - California Institute of Technology, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Polakoff, Murray E. - Texas, University, 1953-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Powers, Perry J. - University of Oregon, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Ratner, Leonard Gilbert - Stanford University, 1955-1957 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Resse, William Lewis - Drake University, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Reeves, Charles H. - Oklahoma, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Riddle, Donald Husted - Hamilton College, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Rochow, Eugene George - Havard University, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Ryan, Alvan S. - Notre Dame, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Ryder, Frank Glessner - Dartmouth College, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Rosenthal, Erich - Queens College, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Schlatter, Richard - Rutgers University, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Schlaretzki, Walter Ernest - Maryland, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Scott, Leland Latham - Mississippi, University of, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Scott, Nathank A. Jr. - Howard University, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Shulenberger, Arvid - Kansas, University of, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Sigworth, Oliver Frederic - Arizona, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Smith, Goldwin - Wayne University, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Smith, James M. - Emory University, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Spaulding, Irving A. - Rhode Island, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Springer, Lawrence A. - Washington, State College of, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Stange, George R. - Minnesota, University of, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Stanley, Oran Bert - Colgate University, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Steinberg, Leo - Parsons School of Design, 1955-1956 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Straton, Owen S. - Wellesley College, 1955 (Box 23 (49684))
      - Stumpf, Samuel Enoch - Vanderbilt University, 1955-1956 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Swain, Robert L. - New York, State University of, 1955-1956 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Swerdlow, Irwin - Dillard University, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Tannenbaum, Edward R. - Colorado Agricultural and Medical College, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Thornborough, Emma Lou - Butler University, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Tossas, Leila V. C. - Polytechnic Institute, 1955-1957 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Trapido, Joel - Hawaii, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Traughott, John L. - Connecticut, University of, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Urban, C. Stanley - Park College, 1955-1956 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Vandermeulen, Daniel C. - Claremeont Men's College, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Vinacke, W. Edgar - Hawaii, University, 1955-1956 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Wegener, Charles W. - Chicago, University of, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - White, Frederic R. - Belott College, 1955-1956 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Williams, William A. - Oregon, University of, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Wolff, Kurt Heinrich - Ohio State University, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Woodring, Carl R. - Wisconsin, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Wright, Kenneth - Kentucky, University of, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Wylie, Laurence - Haverford College, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Young, Edwin - Wisconsin, University of, 1955-1956 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Zenn, Elizabeth - Agnes Scott College, 1955-1956 (Box 24 (49685))
      - Zimansky, Curt A. - Iowa, State University of, 1955 (Box 24 (49685))
    - Administrative Files, 1951-1957
      - List of winners, 1951-1952 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Memoranda to Presidents of Colleges and Universities, 1951-1952 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Announcements, 1952-1953 (Box 25 (49686))
      - List of winners, 1952-1953 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Advisors at Institutions, 1953-1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - List of winners, 1953-1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Memorandum to Fellows, 1953-1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Advisers at Institutions, 1954-1955 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Announcements and applications, 1954-1955 (Box 25 (49686))
      - List of winners, 1954-1955 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Memorandum to Fellow, 1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - List of winners, 1955-1956 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Advisors - Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Advisors - Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Committee on Administration, 1951-1953 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Faculty Fellowship National Committee - General correspondence, 1955 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Faculty Fellowship National Committee - Meetings - Agenda and other meeting materials [12 Folders], 1951-1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Faculty Fellowship National Committee - Reports [2 Folders], 1951-1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Faculty Fellowship Regional Committees - Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Faculty Fellowship Regional Committee - Members - List, 1953-1955 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Faculty Fellowship Regional Committee - New York Readers, 1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Faculty Fellowship Regional Committee - Policy for use of Regional Committees, 1951 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Faculty Fellowhsip Program - Policy and procedure [3 Folders], 1951-1954 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Faculty Fellowhsip Program - Press releases [5 Folders], 1951-1955 (Box 25 (49686))
      - Evaluation reports [6 Folders], 1952-1954 (Box 26 (49687))
      - Tax information - Correspondence and memoranda, 1952-1957 (Box 26 (49687))
  - High School Teachers Fellowship Program, 1951-1966; 8; 22.8 Cubic Feet 19 boxes.; 19 boxes.
    The High-School Teachers Fellowship Program sub-series consists of information on each applicant and their school. The awardee files are arranged in chronological order by the academic year awarded, then alphabetically by the fellow's surname. Also included are files on policy and procedures, statistics and reports. The majority of these files are confidential in nature as the resumes contain financial and personal information. Box 18 contains grant file cards of the Fellowship winners.
    - HSTFP, 1952-1953, 1952-1954
      - Adams, Abby Harris - University High School - Eugene, Oregon, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Alford, Hollis W. - Kermit High School - Kermit, Texas, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Allen, Marjorie - Sotheast High School - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Allen, Otis W. - Greenwod High School - Mississippi, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Andrews, Emily Roberta - McClenaghan High School - Florence, South Carolina, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Armstrong, Patricia Joan - Rocky River High School - Ohio, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Asmussen, Herrold A. C. - Central High School - Sioux City, Iowa, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Aycock, Minnie Enid - Gladewater High School - Gladewater, Texas, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Baker, Maxine - West High School - Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Ballam, Oral L. - North Cache High School - Richmond High School - Richmond, Utah, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Barkhurst, Vernon Laben - Corvallis High School - Oregon, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Bauschard, Hermine Katherine - Academy High School - Erie, Pennsylvania, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Becher, Edmund Theodore - John R. Rogers High School - Spokane, Washington, 1952 - 1954 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Beeler, Ida H. - Donora Junior High School - Donora, Pennsylvania, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Belt, Virginia McKemie - Calvin Coolidge High School - Moline, Illinois, 1952 - 1954 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Berrong, Rita Elizabeth - O'Keefe High School - Atlanta, Georgia, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Bickimer,Laura Ann - John Marshall High School - Cleveland, Ohio, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Bloom, Rose Lillian - Thomas A. DeVilbiss High School - Toledo, Ohio, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Blakemore, James Elliot - Great Neck High School - Great Neck, NY, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Bloom, Samuel - Monree High School - Rochester, NY, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Bonomi, Florence Margaret - Aliquippa High School - Pennsylvania, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Bowles, Ora Lee - Tulsa Central High School - Oklahoma, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Brandon, Robert Kelsey - Celina City School - Ohio, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Britt, Daisie Belle - Ada High School - Oklahoma, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Brodsky, Samuel Morton - Abraham Lincoln High School - Philadelphia, PA, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Brown, Esther Russell - Austin High School - El Paso, Texas, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Brown, Zaida Corrine - Snyder Senior High School - Snyder, Texas, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Buhl, Bertha Marie - New Hartford Central School - New York, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Burnham, Mary Lucille - Wilbur H. Lynch High School - Amsterdam, New York, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Burroughs, Maurine Jameson - Coleman High School - Coleman, Texas, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Butler, Charles Arthur - Jeannette High School - Jeannette, Pennyslvania, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Buttles, Madeline S. - Rutland High School - Rultand Vermont, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Callahan, Genevieve M. - Chateaugay Central School - New York, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Campbell, Chester Lee - Laurinburg High School - North Carolina, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Campos-Soler, Antonia Luisa - Mayaguez High School - Puerto Rico, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Carter, Odessa - Cloverdale High School - Montgomery, Alabama, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Chotvacs, Julius - Central High School - Pueblo, Colorado, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Clark, Marilyn Jean - Plainfield Community High School - Plainfield, Illinois, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Clark, Randolph Duvall - W.E. Greiner High School - Dallas, Texas, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Cleaves, Mildred - Newark High School - Newark, Delaware, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Clement, William Joseph - Bridgehampton High School - New York, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Cobb, William Joseph - New Hope Solebury High School - Pennsylvania, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Cody, Katherine Frances - Drury High School - North Adams, Massachusetts, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Colonius, Dorothy - Alton Senior High School - Alton Illionis (Box 1 (49688))
      - Dean, Kenneth William - Fenger High School - Chicago, Illinois, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Demele, Curt Richard - Berkeley High School - Berkeley, California, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Dingley, John Thomas Jr. - Spalding High School - Griffin, Georgia, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Dobyns, Mable Louise - Shelbyville High School - Illionois, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Douglas, Edna Mae - Dunbar High School - Little Rock, Arkansas, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Douglas, Robert Roderick - Susan Miller Dorsey High School - Los Angeles, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Downey, Margaret Virginia - Gorton High School - Yonkers, New York, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Doyle, Leila Ann - Froebel High School - Gary, Indiana, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Driscoll, Clare - Woodrow Wilson High School - Washington, DC, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Dunning, Arthur Stephenson - Wilson High School - Saint Paul, Minnesota, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Fersh, Seymour H. - New Paltz Central High School - New York, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Findley, Nell Green - Canyon High School - Canyon, Texas, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Fister, Julia A. - Sewanhaka High School - Mineola, New York, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Fitzgerald, William Edward - Shasta Union High School - Redding, California, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Fly, Virginia - Central High School - Evansville, Indiana, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))
      - Fox, Thurman - West High School - Madison, Wisconsin, 1952 - 1953 (Box 1 (49688))